Waiter
服务员
Brother lend me five minutes to be a boyfriend
兄弟借我五分钟当男朋友
You are I am
你就是 我是
This is my boyfriend next to me
旁边这位是我男朋友
I'm here today to promise the middleman
我今天会来是答应中间人
Give two families a face
给两家人一个面子
But wait a minute. I'll tell the middleman
不过等一下我就跟中间人说
Don't introduce this rubbish to me in the future
以后不要介绍这种垃圾给我
Who are you calling trash
你说谁是垃圾
What are you doing
你干嘛
What did I do? I know you
自己干了什么自己清楚你
Find this person to pay for your mobile phone after going out
出去之后找这个人赔你手机
But do this kind of thing later
不过以后再干这种事情
It's not as simple as making a mobile phone
就不是泡个手机这么简单
Do you hear me
听到了吗
Master Xu
徐大少爷
Are you mistaken for someone else
你认错人了吧
He's not Hsu Chin-feng
他不是徐津枫
Miss Chiang
蒋小姐
Nice to meet you
幸会
Miss Jiang Da
蒋大小姐
Forget if you think I'm so ugly in your heart
在你心里觉得我长得那么丑也就算了
Do you think we
难道你认为我们
Will the Xu family let the big lady sit in the hall for a blind date
徐家会让大小姐坐在大厅里相亲吗
You have to speak two minutes later
你要再晚说两分钟
Forget the lobby
别说大厅了
I can dig out three rooms and one living room for you
三室一厅我都能给你抠出来
Nothing, nothing
没什么没什么
I mean
我是说
Master Xu, this meal is too insincere, isn't it
徐少爷这饭请的也太没诚意了吧
This seafood is not fresh
这海鲜都不新鲜了
Since Miss Jiang doesn't like it, let's pour it down
既然蒋小姐不喜欢那就倒了吧
Don't
别呀
I mean, it wouldn't be so wasteful
我是说也不至于这么浪费
You can eat if you make do
凑合凑合也能吃
Since Miss Jiang doesn't like it, change another batch
蒋小姐既然不喜欢那就再换一批
Then I'm not welcome
那我就不客气了
I thought she said she was spoiled
不是说她娇生惯养吗
What happened
什么情况
It looks good
看起来还不错
This is the last piece
这可是最后一块了
I don't want to divide you a little
要不分你一点
Not interested
不感兴趣
It doesn't work well
这招不好使
Do it again somewhere else
换个地方再来一次
If you eat too much, go out and find a place to visit
吃多了出去找个地方逛逛吧
What is the most expensive bag in your shop
你们店最贵的包是哪款呀
The money was flown in from the show two hours ago
俩小时前从秀场空运过来的款
You are a friend of our general manager Xu
您是我们徐总的朋友
Naturally, the VIP price is also 800,000
自然也是VIP价 80万
Isn't it good to meet Miss Jiang for the first time
蒋小姐 第一次见面这样不太好吧
Make it look like our Xu family
弄得好像我们徐家
It's like taking 800,000 bags to deal with you
要拿80万的包应付你一样
How do you do the high-definition that you bought in the show factory today
你好 把今天在秀厂买到的高定
Pack all clothes and bags
无论是衣服还是包全部打包
Send it to Miss Jiang's house
送到蒋小姐家
OK
好的
It seems that Miss Jiang today
看来蒋小姐今天
I have to think a little more about the reasons for rejecting people
又要再多想一点拒绝人的理由了
But it doesn't matter if you can't think of it
不过想不出来也没关系
Looking forward to seeing you next time
期待下次再见
Find this pair of shoes to Miss Jiang's size
把这双鞋找一个蒋小姐的尺码
Get married together
一起结了
It is estimated that Miss Lin will take 40 minutes to drive to your company
林小姐到您公司预计需要40分钟车程
Get in the car and I'll see you off
上车我送你
Auntie, you have a conscience
姑奶奶算你有良心